♪
♪ Another day another bundle size exceeds the limit
I am drowning in a sea of JavaScript frameworks ♪
I am drowning in a sea of JavaScript frameworks
The BFF is broken and the state is out of sync ♪
♪ I am drowning in a sea of JavaScript frameworks
The BFF is broken and the state is out of sync
I'm staring at a screen until my weary eyes go pink ♪
♪ The BFF is broken and the state is out of sync
I'm staring at a screen until my weary eyes go pink
And the bundlers are failing and the tests are turning red ♪
♪ I'm staring at a screen until my weary eyes go pink
And the bundlers are failing and the tests are turning red
I can't remember all the npm commands they said ♪
♪ And the bundlers are failing and the tests are turning red
I can't remember all the npm commands they said
Pathland take me to the place where UI is free ♪
♪ I can't remember all the npm commands they said
Pathland take me to the place where UI is free
Written once in any tongue and rendered flawlessly ♪
♪ Pathland take me to the place where UI is free
Written once in any tongue and rendered flawlessly
Sixty frames of pure perfection running on the line ♪
♪ Written once in any tongue and rendered flawlessly
Sixty frames of pure perfection running on the line
Pathland oh Pathland make your vision finally mine ♪
♪ Sixty frames of pure perfection running on the line
Pathland oh Pathland make your vision finally mine
Fixed sixteen byte opcodes flowing through the wire like blood ♪
♪ Pathland oh Pathland make your vision finally mine
Fixed sixteen byte opcodes flowing through the wire like blood
Washing all the heavyweight frameworks away into the mud ♪
♪ Fixed sixteen byte opcodes flowing through the wire like blood
Washing all the heavyweight frameworks away into the mud
No more client side state models to maintain and then ignore ♪
♪ Washing all the heavyweight frameworks away into the mud
No more client side state models to maintain and then ignore
Only tiny deltas traveling and nothing anymore ♪
♪ No more client side state models to maintain and then ignore
Only tiny deltas traveling and nothing anymore
Pathland take me to the place where UI is free ♪
♪ Only tiny deltas traveling and nothing anymore
Pathland take me to the place where UI is free
Written once in any tongue and rendered flawlessly ♪
♪ Pathland take me to the place where UI is free
Written once in any tongue and rendered flawlessly
Sixty frames of pure perfection running on the line ♪
♪ Written once in any tongue and rendered flawlessly
Sixty frames of pure perfection running on the line
Pathland oh Pathland make your vision finally mine ♪
♪ Sixty frames of pure perfection running on the line
Pathland oh Pathland make your vision finally mine
Pathland take me to the place where UI is free ♪
♪
♪ Pathland oh Pathland make your vision finally mine
Pathland take me to the place where UI is free
Written once in any tongue and rendered flawlessly ♪
♪ Pathland take me to the place where UI is free
Written once in any tongue and rendered flawlessly
Sixty frames of pure perfection running on the line ♪
♪ Written once in any tongue and rendered flawlessly
Sixty frames of pure perfection running on the line
Pathland oh Pathland make your vision finally mine ♪
♪ Sixty frames of pure perfection running on the line
Pathland oh Pathland make your vision finally mine
It works end to end and the tests are green ♪
♪ Pathland oh Pathland make your vision finally mine
It works end to end and the tests are green
Pathland ♪
♪ It works end to end and the tests are green